export const questions = [
    {
        question: "Who is the author of the One Piece manga?",
        suggestions: [
            "Masashi Kishimoto",
            "Tite Kubo",
            "Eiichiro Oda",
            "Akira Toriyama",
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2,
        point: 10,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Luffy's first crewmate?",
        suggestions: ["Sanji", "Usopp", "Zoro", "Nami"],
        correctAnswer: 2,
        point: 10,
    },
    {
        question: "Which Devil Fruit did Luffy originally eat?",
        suggestions: [
            "Mera Mera no Mi",
            "Gomu Gomu no Mi",
            "Hito Hito no Mi",
            "Yami Yami no Mi",
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1,
        point: 10,
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the captain of the Whitebeard Pirates?",
        suggestions: ["Kaido", "Big Mom", "Shanks", "Edward Newgate"],
        correctAnswer: 3,
        point: 10,
    },
    {
        question:
            "What is the name of the sea where the Straw Hat Pirates start their journey?",
        suggestions: ["Grand Line", "East Blue", "Calm Belt", "New World"],
        correctAnswer: 1,
        point: 10,
    },
    {
        question:
            "What is the real identity of the 'Gomu Gomu no Mi' revealed in the Wano arc?",
        suggestions: [
            "Mythical Zoan: Sun God Nika",
            "Paramecia: Rubber Rubber Fruit",
            "Logia: Lightning Fruit",
            "Mythical Zoan: Monkey God",
        ],
        correctAnswer: 0,
        point: 10,
    },
    {
        question:
            "What is the ancient weapon that Robin is searching for through Poneglyphs?",
        suggestions: ["Poseidon", "Pluton", "Uranus", "All of the above"],
        correctAnswer: 3,
        point: 10,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these characters is a member of CP0?",
        suggestions: ["Kaku", "Rob Lucci", "Blueno", "All of the above"],
        correctAnswer: 3,
        point: 10,
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Joy Boy in One Piece lore?",
        suggestions: [
            "A legendary pirate from the past",
            "A title given to the Pirate King",
            "An ancient figure linked to Laugh Tale and the Void Century",
            "A warrior from Elbaf",
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2,
        point: 10,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Which island is known as the final destination of the Grand Line?",
        suggestions: [
            "Fish-Man Island",
            "Sabaody Archipelago",
            "Raftel (Laugh Tale)",
            "Enies Lobby",
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2,
        point: 10,
    },
];

export default questions;
